孩子们
hi,kids.
妈妈，看我做的
Mommy,look what I made.
哦
Oh wow.
是农场
It's a farmer and
有只牛和马，真漂亮
a cow and some horses. It's beautiful.
是给特德办公室的
It's for ted's office.
哦，他肯定喜欢
Oh,he's gonna love it.
如果你管他叫爸爸就更好了
And it would be nice if you called hidad.
给我抱抱
Give me a big hug.
鳄梨是关键
Secret is the haas avocados.
如果你需要我可以把配方邮寄给你
I can e-mail you the recipe if you want.
这是自周五以来他们第三次修改计划了
Oh. This is the third time they've changed plans since friday.
这些白痴以为他们可以加进去14楼,市长不会发现
These idiots think you can just add a 14th floor and the mayor won't notice.
我觉得把停车场改成幼儿园太复杂
I thought turning the garage into a nursery was complicated.
结果你走运了么?
Any luck on your end yet?
至少尝试了
Not for lack of trying.
特德
Ted.
别这样
Come on.
我得去告诉一个客户他是白痴的事实
I have to go tell a client he's an idiot.
跑别处踢屁股去吧
Go kick some ass.
三点我要带斯黛上空手道课
I have to take stella to karate by 3:00
然后去珠丽的生日会
and birthday party at julia's after.
有事么？
You okay?
没事，一会儿回来
Yeah,I'll be back.
保证她把衣服穿好
Just make sure she's dressed.
啊
Ah.
甜心
Honey!
豪斯医生,第二季 第十一集
house,Season 2 Episode 11
他其实挺准时
he's actually on time.
还早了6分钟呢
He's six minutes early.
- 有情况了,- 我接手了
- Something's happened. ,- I'm on it.
早，吉米
Morning,jimmy.
我离开的时候有人死了么?
Anybody die while I was gone?
你……烫衬衫了么?
Did--did you iron your shirt?
本想刮胡子来着，找不到剃刀
Thought about shaving. Couldn't find a razor.
到底在巴尔的摩发生了?
What the hell happened in baltimore?
对不起，头儿,没亲嘴也不泄密
Sorry,chief. Never kiss and tell.
我看你已经透露了
I think you just did.
世界上没有光亲嘴那么回事
There's no such thing as "just a kiss".
你烫衬衫了么?,今天所有人都精神焕发啊
Did you iron your shirt? Everybody's flash today.
她离开马克了么？她打算那么干么？
Has she left mark? Is she going to?
我觉得我听见癌症小孩在叫你了
I think I can hear cancer kids calling.
你打算让她离开马克么?
Are you planning on asking her to leave mark?
不确定
Not sure.
卡麦伦拿走了我的日历
Cameron keeps my calendar.
嘿，这可是个大事,这是婚外情
Hey,this is a big deal. This is an affair.
你到底有没有跟史黛西谈谈这个的含义?
Have you even talked to stacy about what the hell this means?
没那么多谈话的时间
Didn't have a lot of time for talking.
如果你懂我意思的话
If you know what I mean.
太好了，破坏一个婚姻为喜剧创造了,肥沃的土壤
Great. Breaking up a marriage. Fertile ground for high comedy.
我们得谈谈这事儿
We need to talk about this.
天啊，希望可以
Gosh,wish I could.
艾滋病毒试验如何?
How did the hiv tests go?
你研究过了么?
Did you study up?
我重新安排了下午的计划,我们有新病人了
I rescheduled for this afternoon. We have a new patient.
34岁女病人，运动失调
34-year-old female. Movement disorder.
运动失调?
Movement disorder?
有趣
Fascinating.
这可不会随风而去的
This isn't just gonna go away.
当然不会，可希望你能
No. But maybe you will.
可能是车祸造成头部外伤而致
Probably suffered head trauma in the car accident.
外伤造成运动障碍
Trauma leads to the dyskinesia.
据她丈夫说
According to her husband,
扭动是在她还没接近车的时候就开始了
the flailing started before she got anywhere near that car.
是什么样的扭动?
What does the flailing look like?
她的手臂无法控制地抽搐,还伴有轻度的面部抽搐
Her arms spasm uncontrollably,and there's a mild facial twitch.
示范一下?
Demonstration?
你想知道样子，去看看病人不得了
you want to know what it looks like,go see the patient.
哦，挺恶毒啊
Ooh,snarky.
我走了以后他一直都这样么?
Was he like this the whole time I was gone?
病人在过去的13个月里亢奋过度
Patient's been a fertility regiment for the last 13 months.
-系统中过量的雌激素可以解释……,-谁把动物饼干吃完了?
- Excess estrogen in the system could explain-- ,- who finished the animal crackers?
突发的运动失调可能是亨式病症状
sudden movement disorder could be a symptom of huntington'S.
如果吃完了
if you finish something,
就别把空盒子再摆回去,扔出去啊
don't just put back the empty box,throw it out.
亨式病的确诊需要时间,我们该给她用上三苯氧胺
Huntington's takes a day to confirm. We should put her on tamoxifen
以防止亢奋,阻断雌激素分泌
in case it is the fertility meds. Counteract the estrogen.
如果想杀她婴儿，这该是个绝妙的主意
It's a great idea if you want to kill her baby.
运动失调可出现在妊娠最初的三个月里
Movement disorder can present in the first trimester.
她没怀孕
She's not pregnant.
往小棍儿上撒尿的准确度只是99%
Peeing on a stick is only 99% accurate.
做个真正的妊娠测试吧
Get a real pregnancy test.
你知道的，一点血、荷尔蒙和兔子那种
You know,the one with the blood and the hormones and the rabbit.
哦，对不起，豪华轿车还是你的
Oh,I'm sorry. It's still your limo.
那您的意见呢，黛西小姐?
Whaddaya say,miss daisy?
随便你吧
Whatever you want.
- 没用的鸭子不呱呱叫了,- 你叫，有人向你开枪
- Lame duck's done quacking. - You quack,people shoot at you.
卡迪把我放这不过是想让你难受而已
Cuddy just put me here to make you miserable.
再过两天，你坐回来,自己让自己难受吧
Another two days,you can go back to making yourself miserable.
好，先做核磁吧
Okay. Get an mri.
看看是在脑袋里还是尿里
See if it's in her head or in her uterus.
你得把她弄瘫了
You're gonna want to paralyze her.
你给舞蹈病做试验
You run tests on a flailer,
有人会丢只眼睛
somebody's gonna lose an eye.
你认为我怀孕了么?
You think I'm pregnant?
我们要确定一下
We need to find out for sure.
一旦她生产后这一切都会恢复正常么?
Would all this go away once she delivered?
依然有神经系统问题的可能,我们要做核磁
It couldso be neurological. We need to get an mri.
如果她怀孕了的话可以做么?
Can she do that if she's pregnant?
对胎儿的危害甚小
The risk to the fetus is extremely low.
可依然有风险
But there is a risk.
我……我看我们在确定前不该做
I-I don't think we should do it until we're sure.
啊
Ah.
特德，我看你还是带斯黛回家吧
Ted,I think you should take stella home.
我要呆着，我们该陪你
I want to stay here. We should be with you.
你该把她带出去
You should take her out of the room.
我们要暂时停止她的抽搐
We're going to temporarily stop margo's spasms.
- 你能做到么? ,- Vecuronium
- You can do that? ,- Vecuronium.
是一种暂时的瘫痪
It's a paralytic.
其实就是从肌肉上切断大脑
Essentially cuts off the brain from the muscles.
别担心，你妈妈不会有事的
Don't worry. Your mom will be just fine.
那样有助做试验
It'll make running the tests easier.
而且如果怀孕了对胎儿也没有伤害
And it won't be dangerous for the baby if you are pregnant.
- 走吧，斯黛,- 我要跟妈妈在一起
- let's go,stella. - I want to be with mommy.
我们就在外面，得让医生把她治好啊
We'll be just outside. We gotta let the doctors get her better.
没事的，甜心
It's okay,sweetie.
- 爱你,- 爱你
- Love you. ,- Love you.
你所有器官会被严密监视
Your vitals will be watched closely.
我要合上你的眼睑,这样你的眼睛才不会太干
I'm going to close your lids your eyesn't dry out.
放松吧
Just try to relax.
你到底干了什么啊?
What the hell did you do?
就因为你冷还孤独么?
Were you just cold and lonely?
他当然会告诉你，他是个才8岁的小孩
Course he told you,he's an eight-year-old boy.
嘿，你才是那个亲吻他的人
Hey,you're the one who kissed him.
你那么起劲干什么?
Why are you so worked up over this?
- 因为你结婚了,- 又不是跟你
- Because you're married. ,- Not to you.
这没你什么事
This is none of your business.
上次你离开的时候
The last time you left,
我是那个收拾残局的人
I was the one stuck picking up the pieces.
哦，好吧，他每晚哭着入睡,他是那样的人么？
Oh,right. He cried himself to sleep every night. That so sounds like him.
他都害5年相思病了
He's been pining for five years!
- 你太戏剧化了,- 不，实际上，我还没充分发挥呢
- You' being dramatic. ,- No. Actually,I'm underplaying.
是我受了限制
This is me being restrained.
就亲了一下
It was one kiss.
你是装傻呢么?
Are you being intentionally thick?
这可不会只是一夜情
This was not just a one-night stand.
- 你不能耍他 ,- 我没有
- You can't toy with him. ,- I'm not.
没准是他在耍我呢
He's probably toying with me.
我……我不知道我在干嘛
I do--I don't know what I'm doing.
哦，天啊
Oh,boy.
欢迎回来，你已经逃出瘫痪了
Welcome back to the world. You're off the vecuronium.
你能给我动下脚趾么?
Could you wiggle your toes for me?
核磁结果没事
The mri was clear.
总之东西不在脑子里
Whatever this is isn't in your brain.
核磁？
The mri.
那么我没怀孕喽?
So I'm not pregnant?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那么接下来我们干嘛?
So what do we do next?
可能性众多
It could be a variety of things.
有些可治，有些情况就比较严重了
Some treatable. Others more serious.
张嘴
Open up.
要做遗传测试筛除亨式病
We're gonna run a genetic test for huntington'S.
- 最严重的一种么? ,- 是
- That one of the more serious ones? ,- Yeah.
也有可能是亢奋治疗的一种症状
it's also possible that this is just a symptom of the fertility treatments.
现在我们知道你没怀孕,
Now that we know you're not pgnant,
我们会给你用三苯氧胺阻断雌激素分泌
we're going to start you on tamoxifen to counteract the estrogen.
那样是否会使所有亢奋治疗失效?
Will that undo all the fertility treatments?
一时的，对
For the time being,yeah.
但可以治愈你
But it could cure you.
等你健康后你可以重新开始
you can start trying again once we get you healthy.
该死
Damn it!
致瘫剂失效后抽搐会变的更厉害
The spasms are going to get worse now that the vecuronium's wearing off.
你这么害怕干嘛?
What are you so scared of?
我还是你妈妈，不过生了点小病
I'm still your mother. I'm just a little sick.
你干嘛要把她带来,我跟你说了把她留在家里
Why did you even bring her here? I told you to leave her at home!
突发易激惹
hypervigilance,sudden irritability--
是……跟卡迪共进午餐的症状?
symptomatic of... lunch with cuddy?
病人可确诊为亨式病
The patient now defines huntington'S.
那你还需要我干嘛?
Then what do you need me for?
开始用亨式病的药就是了
Start her on huntington's meds.
等拿到结果?
Before we get her test results back?
如果用丙戊酸，她的肝脏就完了
If we start her on valproic acid,it could destroy her liver.
会中风
Could stroke.
如果等，可能会毁坏整个神经系统
If we wait,she could progress to full blown psychosis.
那她的孩子就永远没机会说再见了
Then her kid will never get the chance to say good-bye.
想告诉同学那样的感觉么?
Want to tell the class how that feels?
亨式病不会在一天里击垮整个精神系统
Huntington's patients don't progress to psychosis in a day.
她可以创个记录
She went from 0 to 60 in world-record time.
也没准根本就不是亨式病
Indicating it might be something other than huntington'S.
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
离我远点
Stay away from me.
我女儿在哪？发生什么事了？
Where's my daughter? What's happening?
她精神崩溃了
She's having a psychotic break.
她不是你的孩子,你怎么会关心?
She is not yours.What do you ?
- 冷静 ,- 马戈，你会伤到人的
- Calm down. ,- Margo,you're gonna hurt someone.
推两毫升ativan
Push two milligrams of ativan.
我要我女儿
I want my daughter!
她不是你的，我要我女儿
She's not yours. I want my daughter.
不做试验了
No more experiments.
不
No!
她的亨式病测试怎么会是阴性呢?
how can her huntington's test be negative?
症状都有啊
all the signs are there.
运动失调、精神系统问题
Movement disorder,psychosis.
该是亨式病
It should be huntington'S.
是啊，那你的工作就容易多了
Yeah. That'd certainly make your job easier.
对马戈来说是好消息,不是亨式病
Well,good news for margo,it's not huntington'S.
对我们是坏消息
Bad news for us.
她的精神崩溃抵消了亢奋药物
Her psychotic break eliminates fertility meds.
这意思是我们根本不知道她出啥毛病了
Which means we have no idea what's wrong with her.
我们的付出那么多,你的给予那么少
We give you so much. You give us so little.
你知道，病人在壮年原发精神分裂症
You know,patient is prime age to develop spontaneous schizophrenia.
几乎是不可能的
almost impossible.
家族无精神病史
No family history of mental illness.
毒素呢?
How about toxins?
她家没有病人，她办公室没有,她的志愿者工作组没有
None of her family members are sick. Nobody at her office, her volunteer group,
孩子的班级、家长会，都没有
kid's classes, and pta members. All fine.
所以，她养育女儿，做生意
So she raises a daughter,runs a business,
她从事慈善事业
she does charity work.
在学校做义工，还参加家长会
She volunteers at school. Attends pta.
怎么能让妈妈运转呢?
What makes mommy run?
你在考虑毒品么?
You thinking drugs?
可卡因
Cocaine.
可以解释精神问题和舞蹈病症状
Explains the psychosis and the flailing.
已经那么多离奇精力，买咸肉,在锅里煎
And the uncanny ability to bring home the bacon, fry it up in a pan,
还要记得别忘了让特德觉得是个男人
and never ever let teddy forget that he's a man.
我去查查看
I'll go look for her stash.
带上福满
Take foreman.
陈词滥调需要理由
There's gotta be a reason for the stereotype.
我知道你在那里头
I know you're in there.
我能听见你的关心
I can hear you caring.
门是锁着的
The door was locked.
意思就是我不想见任何人
Means I didn't want to see anyone.
高中同学团聚么?
High school reunion?
给一个病人的，她没法卷
It's for a patient. She can't roll.
把那个门也锁上
Now lock that door too.
妄想狂
Paranoia.
一定是好料
Must be the good stuff.
这样的时候我老想得癌症
Times like these,I wish I had cancer.
她说什么了?
So what did she say?
那要看情况,你干嘛了，我们谈的是谁？
That depends. What did you do,and who are we talking about?
我们都知道我俩刚说完
We both know that as soon as we talked,
你就会跑到史黛西那传话、傻笑
you ran to stacy so you could gossip and giggle.
我需要知道她说什么了
I need to know what she said.
我有个疯狂的主意,你干嘛不找她谈呢?
I have a crazy idea. Why don't you go talk to her?
因为我最好的朋友告诉我,那会带来麻烦的
Because my bestest buddy says that could lead to trouble.
她听上去挺困扰,可我不相信
She sounds confused, but I don't think she is.
我看她是要看你的行动,让她觉得你是认真的
I think she's waiting for you to do something. Show her you're serious.
哇
Wow.
从失贞到干她可是个大飞跃
It's a big jump from infidelity is morally wrong to do her.
我没说干她，我说的是行动
I didn't say do her. I said do something.
她到底说了什么?
What exactly did she say?
她没说是个错误
She didn't say it was a mistake.
她不会在马克康复的时候就抛弃他
She's not gonna leave mark in the middle of his rehab.
太内疚了
Too much guilt.
她抛弃了你
She left you.
够刺耳的，老兄
Harsh toke,dude.
豪斯
House.
毁灭享受
Killjoy.
我掩护不了这个
I could've covered this.
你今天得做了那个试验
You need to get that test today.
我希望你们能记住我的生日,而不是我做艾滋病试验的日子
I wish you guys remember my birthday instead of my hiv test.
原谅我们关心你吧
Forgive us for being concerned.
我跟豪斯打了赌
I got a bet with house.
他说你太害怕不会去拿结果
He says you're too scared to get it.
我说你太拘谨了一定会拿
I say you're too anal not to.
我切入到主题了吧
I'll cut you in.
真浪费
that was a colossal waste.
谁知道呢？
who would've known?
搜查一个大家庭,以查找非法毒品简直太明显了
Searching a high end family home for illicit narcotics was such an obvious choice.
有工作的妈妈大部分时间是在车上的
Working moms practically live in their cars.
跑步时撞的?
Little bump on the run?
你是拖车贼，是吧?
You were a car thief,right?
哈
Ha.
妈妈的小助手
Mama's little helper.
豪斯
House.
利他林
Ritalin.
pg等级的可卡因
Cocaine with a pg rating.
是她女儿的处方
Prescribed to her daughter.
这年月妈妈为了家庭无所不为
Mommy does everything for her family these days.
甚至是他们的药片
Even swallows their pills.
可能孩子的药就是孩子的药
It's possible the kid's meds are the kid's meds.
吃足够的利他林，症状都能解释
Pop enough ritalin,it can explain everything.
利他林没准能解释一些……
Well,ritalin maybe explains some tics,some involuntary--
类似舞蹈病的运动症状
case reports have referred to chorea.
可她已被切断供给了,
She's been cut off from her stash,
她的舞蹈病症状和精神系统问题,没有反复，很好
so the flailing's tapered off and the psychosis hasn't returned.It's perfect.
氧化测试会证明的
Tox screen will confirm that.
半衰期是12小时，药品已经排出了
Half-life's 12 hours. The drugs'll be out of her system.
我们没事了，放过她吧
We're done. Get rid of her.
我们还有事
We're not done.
我们得确诊，以防她回家死于其他症状
We have to confirm the diagnosis before we send her home to die of something else.
哦对啊，权力的味道太好了
Oh yes,the power tastes so sweet.
你就是无法抗拒
You just can't resist.
你就象糖尿病人在冰琪凌柜台一样
You're like a diabetic at the ice cream counter.
你想拒绝
You want to say no,
可太需要那个巧克力味的了
but you need that chocolaty goodness.
对，是，我还是签字的人啊
Yeah. Well,I'm still signing the charts.
所以，到明天以前,你还没得到杀人许可
So until tomorrow,you're not allowed to kill anyone.
胆小鬼
Wuss.
我们问了她三次她是否用药
We've asked her three times if she's on any meds.
那我们就别问她了
So we don't ask her.
卖糖果的把戏
Candy striper.
你喜欢狗么?
So you like dogs?
那不是狗
That's not a dog.
聪明孩子
Smart kid.
你总是这样乖的小孩么
Are you always such a good little girl,
还是有时妈妈会说你是她喝双份,马提尼的原因?
or does mommy sometimes say you're the reason she needs a double martini?
你是谁?
Who are you?
过来，孩子，我跟你说话呢
Over here,kiddo. I'm talking to you.
集中精神
Focus.
肯定是，因为你没有药了
It must be because you're off your meds.
你是谁?
Who are you?
医生和卖糖果的
Doctor and candy striper.
她没在服药
She's not on any medication.
那就怪了，因为这个瓶子上有她的名字
Well,that's strange cause this bottle has her name on it.
而我认为这里面有治病的药
And I think these are medical pills inside.
他说什么呢?
What's he talking about?
医生开给斯黛...
Doctor prescribed stella...
几个月以前
a few months ago.
我没跟你说因为我没给她吃
I never told you about it because I never gave her any.
哦，那很有趣
Hmm. That's funny
因为瓶子都快空了
cause the bottle's almost empty.
你有几天没吃
You missed a couple of days.
- 吃5片吧,- 停
- Take five. - Stop.
- 你需要水么，甜心? ,- 我没用利他林
- Do you need some water,sweetie? ,- I'm not taking ritalin.
拜托
Come on.
很多酷妈妈都用的
All the cool moms are doing it. And
而且氧化测试显示你也很酷
tox screen says you're cool too.
你在照顾斯黛的时候还用毒品么?
You were on drugs while takingare of stella?
对不起，特德
I'm sorry,ted.
这是自助餐厅的菜单
It's a cafeteria menu.
需要几个小时稳定她
It should take a couple of hours to process her.
然后你可以把她带回家跟她离婚
Then you can take her home and divorce her.
工作晚了么?
Working late?
还是故意躲着马克?
Or you just avoiding mark?
只是个吻，格里
It was one kiss,greg.
到目前为止
So far.
我有计划的
I'm planning on keeping a chart.
我要搬去短山，我看是时候了
I'm moving back to short hills. I think it's time.
你要离开了么?
You're leaving?
本来就不是永久性的,现在马克好的很多
It's never meant to be permanent now that mark's getting better.
是啊，很多
Yeah. Much better.
就差走路了
Except for the whole walking thing.
他需要恢复工作
He needs to get back to work.
是啊
Right.
挽救下一代选错痤疮膏
Saving the next generation from making bad choices about acne cream.
你逃走因为那个吻有它的意思
You're running away because the kiss meant something.
我没逃走，我是回家
I'm not running away. I'm going home.
跟马克
With mark.
我爱马克
I love mark.
你更爱我
You love me more.
我不要你离开
I don't want you to leave.
我们没事吗?
Are we okay?
- 我很抱歉,- 我们还是回家吧
- I'm sorry. ,- Let's just get you home.
好主意
That's a good idea.
- 妈妈,- 嘿!
- Mommy! - Hey!
- 呼叫 ,- 怎么了，妈妈?
- Call the code. - What's wrong,mommy?
出什么事了?
What's going on?
最好是重要事
This better be important.
你得马上回来
You've gotta come back in.
- 不，我不 ,- 马戈本来已经稳定了，但是……
- No,I don'T. ,- Margo's stable,but--
哦，我的天啊，我马上就到
oh,my god. Well,I'll be right there.
她中风了
She had a stroke.
太好了
Perfect.
得回去工作
Gotta go back to work.
现在?
Right now?
嗯
Well
病人稳定
patient's stable.
等半个小时吧
Could maybe wait a half hour.
他该20分钟前就回来的
He should've been here 20 minutes ago.
怀疑他是否全干了
Doubt if he makes it all.
我看到他跟史黛西一起走的
I saw him leave with stacy.
他也许只是送她到车那
He's probably just walking her to her car.
哦，是啊，听起来倒象是豪斯
Oh,yeah. That sounds like house.
他不是白痴,才不会跟个已婚女人勾搭呢
He's not an idiot. He's not going to hook up with a married woman.
我倒希望他能，也许能变得温和一点
I hope he is getting some. Maybe he'll mellow out.
怎么耽搁这个久啊？现在是半夜
what took you so long? It's midnight.
路上不好走
Traffic. Cinco de mayo.
你欠我100块
You owe me 100 bucks.
你没做试验?
You didn't take the test?
拘谨无法战胜恐惧
Fear trumps anal every time.
没什么了不起
It's not a big deal.
我做了滤过性病毒填充和抗体测试
I had the viral load and antibody tests.
99.9% 我没有艾滋病毒
99.9% that I don't have hiv.
如果你做了试验又是阴性的,你就赢了1赔10的赔率
and if you had the test and it's negative, you gain a tenth of a point.
如果是阳性的，你就输了...
But if it's positive, you lose...
近100，对吧?
nearly 100,right?
无心率失常
No arrhythmia.
所以利他林不是关键问题
So ritalin isn't the big problem.
有其他事
Something else is going on.
好吧
Fine.
我们玩医生的游戏吧
Let's play doctors.
我移除了导致中风的凝块
I removed the clot which caused the stroke.
问题是我们不知道它打哪来的
Problem is,we don't know where it came from.
给她心脏、手臂和腿都做了超声波检查,没有问题
Did ultrasounds of her heart,arms,and legs. All clear.
可能是c蛋白不足
Could be a protein c deficiency.
解释不了运动失调
Wouldn't explain the movement disorder.
没什么东西能解释一切
Nothing explains everything.
如果是团伙犯罪呢?
What if it's a crime syndicate?
我们假设：利他林和亢进药物结合出击
Let's say ritalin and the fertility meds plotted a caper.
利他林形成精神症状和舞蹈病
Ritalin takes care of the psychosis,the flailing.
- 我还是觉得利他林…… ,- 亢进药物被自然竞争
- I still don't think ritalin--  ,- fertility meds are competitive by nature.
他们会造就大事件,超乎想像的大事件
They gotta do something bigger. Something really unexpected.
亢进治疗已知可导致子宫内膜癌
fertility treatments have been known to cause endometrial cancer.
也能导致凝块
Which could cause clots.
也可能导致她中风
Which could've caused her to stroke.
所以这次给她的子宫做超声波吧
So ultrasound her uterus this time.
看是不是里面,长了什么不受欢迎的东西
See if there's something growing in there at doesn't look adorable a ones.
卡麦伦
Cameron.
我爱你
I love you.
明天去取试验结果吧
Get your test results tomorrow.
给我心脏下的处方
The prescription for my heart condition.
便宜了点
A bit on the cheesy side.
我在尝试浪漫手段
I was trying for romantic.
还是很合适
Still fits.
告诉马克了么?
Did you tell mark?
我跟他说会工作很晚
I told him I had to work late.
你打算告诉他吗?
You going to tell him?
我怎么告诉他啊?
How am I going to tell him?
还在考虑措词
Still working on that phrasing.
我们最初到这你说“什么都知道”,那样的话怎么了？
How about,"know all the stuff"you worried about when we first came here,honey,
你是对的
you were right."
精练
Pithy.
如果你不在意会伤到什么人的时候,一切都简单化了
Everything's easy when you don't care if you hurt anyone.
你已经把伤害那部分做完了
You already did the hurting part.
- 他只是不知道罢了 ,- 如果我永远不告诉他，他不会受伤
- He just doesn't know yet. - If I never tell hi it'll never hurt.
我不想爱马克
I want not to love mark.
我想恨你，我想一切都简单化
I want to hate you. I want allf this to be simple,
可就不是
but it's not.
你可以要么跟我过,
You can either have a life with me,
要么跟他过
or you can have a life with him.
不是兼顾
It can't be both.
很容易，确实简单
It's that easy. But it is simple.
子宫内膜未见增厚
No endometrial thickening.
- 无杂物,- 无癌症
- No masses. ,- No cancer.
她正接手亢进治疗，产生了血液凝块,就在那
She's on fertility treatments. She had a blood clot. It's there.
上百万的女人接手亢进治疗,并不得癌症
Millions of women are on fertility treatments, and they don't get cancer.
对，他们生孩子
Right. They get babies.
她却是血液凝块和中风
She had a blood clot and a stroke.
她会再来一次，如果我们不快点,找到肿瘤，她会死
She'll get another one and probably die if we don't find that tumor.
做子宫内膜活检
Do an endometrial biopsy.
活检很痛苦也没必要
Biopsy's painful and unnecessary.
我们刚做过超声波
We just did an ultrasound.
- 什么? ,- 嘘
- What? ,- Ssh.
如果你的私人问题干扰了……
If you have a person issue that's interfering with--
嘘
ssh,ssh,ssh.
我们等什么?
What are we waiting for?
你的四周任期刚到期了
Your four weeksjust expired.
你的恐怖通知结束了
Your reign of terror is over.
我的刚开始
Mine is just begun.
现在将小棍儿插进她的洞洞,找到那块癌吧
No go stick a needle up her hoo-hoo and find that cancer.
洞洞?
Hoo-hoo?
他去过霍普金
He went to hopkins.
酒精激发了1500马力的动力……
...has got 1,500 horsepower blown and injected with alcohol.
是啊，那个宝贝真的动起来了
yeah,that baby really moves.
哦，传动...
oh yeah,the transmission...
你看什么呢?
what are you watching?
电视
Tv.
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
特德跟妈妈在一起
Ted's with my mom.
他让护士看我
He asked the nurse to watch me.
什么护士?
What nurse?
她没看好我
She's not really watching me.
明白了
I got that.
你还有气球么?
Do you still have the balloons?
没了
No.
- 你想玩什么么? ,- 不想
- You want play something? - No.
妈妈什么时候能回家?
When can mommy come home?
不知道
Don't know.
你脚怎么了?
What's wrong with your foot?
- 打仗受伤 ,- 疼么?
- War wound. - Does it hurt?
每天疼
Every day.
那就是你难过的原因么?
Is that why you're so sad?
哦，你真可爱
Oh,aren't you adorable.
我不难过，我复杂
I'm not sad, I'm complicated.
小鸡刨的
Chicks dig that.
有一天你会懂的
One day,you'll understand.
我父母有事瞒我时就这么说
That's what my parents say when they don't want me to know something.
他们总说么?
They say that a lot?
只有在讨论生孩子的时候
Only when they're talkingabout making babies and stuff.
当你逮到他们打架的时候?
When you catch them  fighting?
他们不打架
They don't fight.
从不?
Not ever?
彼此相爱的人不打架
People who love each other don't fight.
对，算了
Right. Forgot that.
看你的护士在几楼?
What floor was that nurse onwho was watching you?
二楼
Two.
聊的不错
Good talk.
在你的岁数，子宫内膜癌
At your age,the type of uterine cancer that develops
不会转移
is not likely to metastasize.
很容易治疗
It's very treatable.
别动，马戈
Hold still,margo.
我，觉得有点晕
I'm--I'm feeling a little bit dizzy.
哦，上帝
Oh,my god.
血压降下来了
bp's dropping.
出什么事了?
What's going on?
把她弄出去
get him out of here.
- 发生什么? ,- 心率98，还在升
- What's going on? ,- heart rate's 98 and rising.
我们得把出血的地方找到
We gotta find that bleed.
你要干嘛？扎动脉么？
What'd you do? Hit an artery?
用什么？我还没走手续呢
With what? I hadn't even started the procedure.
哦
Oh!
我需要意见
I need some advice.
不管是什么，能等么?
Whatever it is,can it wait?
能
Yeah.
我走以后格里什么样?
What was greg like after I left?
极端利己，自我陶醉的麻烦分子
Uh,an egomaniacal narcissistic pain in the ass.
跟你离开前一样
Same as before you left.
你认为他能承担一段真正的感情么?
Do you think he's capable of having a real relationship?
巴尔的摩发生什么了?
What happened in baltimore?
- 没事,- 是哦
- Nothing. ,- Right.
- 也许有事 ,- 是哦
- Maybe something. ,- Right.
从技术上说，事情发生在巴尔的摩之后
Technically,most of the something happened after baltimore.
哦上帝，史黛西
Oh god,stacy.
我不知道怎么做
I don't know what to do.
你真要认真考虑离开马克么?
Are you seriously thinking about leaving mark?
没，我不知道
No. I don't know.
我不能
I can'T.
你是想让我告诉那没事么?
And you want me to tell you it's okay?
跟格里在一起不都是坏事,我有理由跟他在一起
It wasn't all bad with greg. I was with him for a reason.
你离开他也有理由
You left him for a reason.
我发誓跟他一起很有趣
I could swear I remember him being fun.
抱歉让你受惊了
Sorry for the scare.
告诉我他没事了
Just tell me she's okay.
超声波显示出血来自肝脏
Ultrasound showed the bleed was coming from her liver.
很罕见，但血液进入了她的输卵管
It's rare,but t blood got into her fallopian tubes.
另一方面，我们很幸运,知道我们先前的方向错了
In a way,it was lucky. Let us know we were looking in the wrong place.
肿瘤在她的肝脏
The tumor's in her liver.
是癌症么?
Is it cancer?
我们正在做试验
We're running some more tests.
这里
There it is.
是肝脏肿瘤
It's a liver tumor.
如果是恶性的
If it's malignant,
她至少让一个孩子变成了没妈的孩子
at least she's only gonna leave one child without a mother.
做活检吧
Do a biopsy.
不能
We can'T.
是动脉
It's vascular.
豪斯
house.
什么事?
What?
我在这跟史黛西有关
I'm here about stacy.
她怎么了?
What about her?
我看我要失去她了
I think I'm losing her.
你妻子，是你的事
Your wife,your problem.
她不跟我说
She won't talk to me.
那你就跟我说么？,跟你的心理医生说去
So what,you're gonna talk to me instead? Talk to your shrink.
她老说什么都没事
She keeps saying everything's fine.
找个酒吧跟陌生人说去吧
Find a bar and talk to a stranger.
你是唯一一个经历过此事的人
You're the only one who's been through this.
我不对她负责
I'm shutting her out.
我老是说那种让我自己生气的话
I'm saying things and then hating myself for saying them.
你是怎么熬过去的?
How did you get past that?
还没
Didn'T.
你就不能当一分钟的人跟我谈谈吗?
Can you please be a human being for one minute and talk to me?
抱歉，得走了，有人要死
Sorry. Gotta go. People dying.
你躲不了我
You're not gonna outrun me.
豪斯
House.
你还不能这样
You're not ready for this.
我看到你跟史黛西说话的方式
I've seen the way you and stacy talk to each other.
你是白痴
You're an idiot.
你没准把你的康复又拖后了三个月
You probably just set your rehab back three months.
放开我，放开我
Let go of me! Get off of me!
肝脏肿瘤不合理
Liver tumor doesn't make sense.
你是说ct错了么?
are you saying the ct was wrong?
我是说症状不合理
I'm saying the symptoms don't add up.
a＋b不等于肝脏肿瘤
"A" plus "b" does not equal liver tumor.
我们得把x解了
We gotta solve for X.
我们得不同看待
We gotta look at this differently.
我们对她知道多少?
What do we know about her?
利他林的副作用是……
Side effects of ritalin caused the--
不，我们把病例已经研究个底朝上了
no. We've examined the file up and down.
过来，给我
Come here. Give me that.
为什么你们总不重视人类的要件呢?
Why do you people always overlook the human element?
我们对她了解什么?
What do we know about her?
马戈...
Margo...
道顿，女人
dalton. The woman.
她很讨人喜欢
She's a people pleaser.
她不想让人失望
She doesn't like to let people down.
从不与丈夫争吵
Who never fights with her husband.
她不求助所以依赖毒品
She went to drugs instead of asking for help to manage her life.
所以，如果她现在不能安排了
So if she can't manage now,
她干嘛再想要个孩子呢?
why does she want another kid?
福满
Foreman.
需要你的帮助
Need your help here.
如果要干个银行的活
You want to pull a bank job.
你会独个去么?
Would you go it alone?
如果只是抢劫一个家，没问题,一、两个同伴就行了
If you're gonna rob a home,sure. It's a one or two man crew.
但是，银行...
But a bank...
望风的，开车的
lookout,getaway driver.
在比喻的结果出来之前,我是不会说话的
I'm not saying anything until the metaphor plays itself out.
所以，毛病在这
So here's the caper.
亢进治疗产生了一个小插曲
Fertility meds create a distraction.
妈妈在过去的三周里,补充了三次利他林
Mommy had three refills on the ritalin in the last three weeks.
团队朝顶楼冲去
That team goes straight for the top floor.
通讯没有问题
Has no problem taking out communications.
但他们还是需要个专家
But they also need a specialist.
开保险箱的
Safe cracker.
这家伙需要干的只是,中风、血液凝块、肝脏肿瘤
All this guy does is stroke,blood clot,liver tumor.
福满对了
Foreman was right.
这该死的家伙还调情呢
This bad ass even does flling.
拜托
Come on.
我知道只有一个家伙干那样的事
Only one guy I know does that kind of work.
避孕药?
Birth control pills?
当外科医生切下你一大块肝脏的时候
While the surgeons are cutting out a chunk of your liver,
我是不是让他们把你的子宫也切了？
should I have them do a hysterectomy too?
切子宫?
A hysterectomy?
我要怀孕呢
I'm trying to get pregnant.
你不用跟我说谎
You don't have to lie to me.
我们又没结婚
We're not married.
你是超级妈妈
You're super mom.
你什么都能干
You can do anything.
你一周工作7天
You work seven days a week.
你是志愿者，带孩子
You volunteer. Raise a kid.
你还有时间跟2号丈夫说
Yet you still somehow find the time to lieto hubby number two
你很想给他一个孩子
that you really really want to give him a child
长着他的下巴和漂亮的褐色眼睛
with his chin and pretty brown eyes.
- 你怎么觉得我……,- 因为合适
- What makes you think that I-- ,- because it fits.
避孕药导致肝腺体瘤
Birth control pills caused hepatocellular adenoma.
解释了所有无法解释的症状
Explains all your symptoms that aren't explained
就这样?
That's it?
同时
Also.
我还会长瘤子
I'll have the tuna on rye.
现在可以离开我房间了么?
Would you like to leave my room now?
肿瘤是良性的
Tumor is benign.
停药后会自然消除，我把手术取消
Stop taking the pill,and it'll go away on its own. I'm canceling the surgery.
你要怎么告诉我丈夫?
What are you going to tell my husband?
我取消手术
That I'm canceling the surgery.
你解释吧
You can do the explaining.
很狡猾吧?
It's tricky,huh?
说不能生孩子
It's one thing to say you can't have a baby.
跟说不想要孩子是两回事
It's another to say you don't want one.
要是我，我会编其他借口
Personally,I'd make up some other lie.
我会……
Could--
我会死在手术台上吗？
could I die on the table?
你告诉他真相会死么?
Could you die if you tell him the truth?
我需要那手术
I need the surgery.
我没吃药
I'm not on the pill.
你不能取消手术
You can't cancel the surgery.
如果她不吃药了，肿瘤会自动消失
If she goes off the pill, the tumor goes away on its own.
你无法证明避孕药导致这些
You have no proof the birth control pills caused this.
你都无法证明她在用
You have no proof she's even taking them.
如果我们手术，她会死在台上
Well,if we do the survey,maybe we'll kill her on the table.
尸检时我就可以证明我对
Then I can prove I'm right at the autopsy.
或者我们可以不做手术,让瘤子长大后杀死她
Or we can forget the surgery, let the tumor grow,and kill her.
你跟史黛西商量一下吧?
Why don't you take iup with stacy?
看哪个风险更小
See which option minimizes your risk.
我想她会说
Here's what I think she's going to say.
“哦，我爱格里”
Oh,I love greg.
但如果你违背病人的愿望,那就是管她叫骗子
But if you go against a patient's wishes, you're calling her a liar.
而如果出问题
And if something goes wrong,
结果我就得上庭对抗大、刻薄大夫
I end up in court having to defend the big,mean doctor albeit with dreamy eyes
尽管我有梦一样的大眼睛,却不相信乡村妈妈
who wouldn't believe the nice suburban mom.
尽管他的拐杖让我融化,还是做那该死的手术吧
And even though his cane makes me melt, do the damn surgery.
耸人听闻
Shocking.
是良性的
It's benign.
人们为了爱做疯狂的事
People do crazy things for love.
不，疯狂是整天在公园闲逛,跟鸽子说话
No. Crazy is hanging out at the park all day talking to pigeons.
她知道自己在干嘛
Rgo knowswhat she's doing.
她放弃半个肝挽救婚姻
She gave up half her liver to save her marriage.
不，她魔术般转移了指纹挽救了谎言
No. She surgically removed her fingerprints to cover her pathetic lie.
扭曲而富于操纵，明白了
It's twisted and manipulative,I get that.
但同时...
But it's also...
很浪漫
romantic.
我连撒尿都懒得放下厕板
I'm barely willing to put the seat down after I pee.
- 我们非说话么? ,- 不，我没事
- Do we need to talk? - Nope. I'm fine.
手术拿出了整个肿瘤
so the surgeon got the whole tumor.
- 是良性的 ,- 不错，是吧?
- And it was benign. ,- That's good,right?
对，良性不错
Yeah. Benign is good.
良性肿瘤怎么会有那么多症状呢?
How could a benign tumor have caused all the symptoms?
我们相信你太太,所有的症状都会消失了
We believe all your wife's symptoms will go away now.
哦，感谢主
Oh. Thank god.
你看，我会去接斯黛
Look. I'm gonna pick up stella.
我找到保姆后给你电话
I'll call you after I get the baby-sitter.
福满医生
Dr. Foreman,
你能帮我
you can help me.
你可以告诉我丈夫...
You could tell my husband that...
因为这些...
because of all this...
我不能再接受亢进治疗了
I can't take any more fertility treatments.
保密原则让我不能告诉你丈夫实情
Confidentiality rules stop me from telling your husband the truth.
但我照义务撒谎到此结束
But my obligation to lie ends there.
有没有……
Are--are there--
有没有一种控制生育的,方法不让我难受的?
is there a birth control method, something that won't make me sick?
马戈，你将需要面对一切冒险了
Margo,you're gonna have risks with everything.
尤其是如果你不打算,告诉你的亢进治疗医生
Especially if you're not telling your fertility doctor.
如果你继续这样做,会毁了你的婚姻和你自己
If you keep doing this,it's gonna kill your marriage and kill you.
你不知道
You don't know.
几年内
In a few years,
我们会放弃
we'll give up,
不再尝试怀孕
stoprying to get pregnant.
我们会拥抱、哭泣
We'll hug,cry.
最终，特德会忘记这回事
Eventually,ted will stop thinking about it.
他会更喜欢斯黛
And he'll appreciate stella even more.
我们就可以幸福生活余下的50年
And we'll live happily together for the next 50 years.
有些事你得知道
Something you need to see.
知道永远都比不知道好
Knowing is always better than not knowing.
这是推荐建议
It's a referral request.
是啊
Right.
艾滋病检查结果早来了
Hiv thing came in earlier.
你没事
You're fine.
你连自己的信都不看却看我的?
You won't read your mail, but you'll open mine?
它说是机密
It said confidential.
我想知道
I wanted to know.
我一生中最重要的信
The most important letter of my life.
你还是个讨厌鬼
And you're still an ass.
令人感到安慰，是吧?
Comforting,isn't it?
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
我今晚要跟马克谈
I'm going to talk to mark tonight.
然后我会在这跟你一起
Then I'm going to stay here with you.
别
Don't do it.
这不好玩，格里
This isn't funny,greg.
我知道
I know.
你...
You...
花了这么多个月追我，我回来了,你却要跑？
spent all these months chasing me. Now I'm here and you start running.
什么变了?
What the hell changed?
没有
Nothing.
什么都没变
Nothing changes.
我不会变
I'm not going to change.
谁让你变了?
Who asked you to?
马克愿意做任何事
Mark is willing to do whatever it takes.
我不会
I'm not.
永远都不会
Never was.
现在你要反省了？,那天晚上我们谈了那么多
Now you're introspective? Weren't so analytical the other night.
你跟马克在一起很快乐,你还会快乐的
You were happy with mark. You'll be happy again.
别说马克了,你怎么了?
Shut up about mark. What the hell's wrong with you?
我没法让你快乐
I can't make you happy.
什么?
What?
你觉得这会怎么结束?
How do you think this is gonna end?
我们为什么而快乐?
We'll be happy for what?
几个星期，几个月
A few weeks,few months.
然后我会无心地说些什么,或者忽视你
And then I'll say something insensitive,or I'll start ignoring you.
开始的时候没事
And at first it'll be okay.
豪斯还是豪斯.
It's just house being house.
然后
And then
在某些地方，你会需要更多
at some point, you will need something more.
你会需要有人给你我不能给你的
You'll need someone who can give you something I can'T.
你知道我是对的，我们经历过
You know I'm right.  I've been there before.
哦
Oh.
不必如此
It doesn't have to be.
有必要
It does.
我不想再经历一次
I don't want to go there again.
对不起，史黛西
I'm sorry,stacy.
50块，打赌他们一年内会离婚
50 bucks says they're divorced in a year.
顶多6个月
Six months tops.
我赌
I'll take that bet.
那是个完美的婚姻
It's the perfect marriage.
如果你不说，就没什么好吵的
There nothing to fight over if you never talk about anything.
你怎么跟她说的?
What did you tell her?
我跟她说别指望我
I told her she's better off without me.
哈
Huh.
没准是对的
That's probably true.
你是白痴
You're an idiot.
你不觉得她该不要指望你么？
You don't think she'd be better off without you.
对，我是一时兴起
Right. I set her off on a whim.
你不明白为什么你让她走
You have no idea why you sent her off.
-别这样 ,-这不是伟大的牺牲
- Don't do this. - This was no great sacrifice.
你让她走因为你必须得很悲惨
You sent her away because you've got to be miserable.
那种破精神分析理论帮你的病人,渡过长夜吧?
That kind of psycho-crap help get your paents through the long nights?
还是专为你造的?
Or is it just for you?
坚韧的爱让你感觉良好? 帮助人感受痛苦
Tough love make you feel good? Helping people feel their pain.
你不喜欢自己
You don't like yourself.
可你钦佩自己
But you do admire yourself.
你就剩下这些了，所以你抓住不放
It's all you've got,so you cling to it.
你深恐如果你改了
You're so afraid if you change,
你会失去使你独特的东西
you'll lose what makes you special.
悲惨没让你比任何人强，豪斯
Being miserable doesn't make you better than everybody else,house.
只是让你悲惨而已
It just makes you miserable.